A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, general correspondence, RG 2, 1971-1980 FA401
Rockefeller Archive Center
- General Correspondence, 1977
  - United States, 1977; 1977/200
    - Ohio State University (L-V), 1977 (Reel 30, Frame 785)
    - Oklahoma State University (Allison, H. Jack), 1977 (Reel 31, Frame 1)
    - Oa-Om, 1977 (Reel 31, Frame 8)
    - Oregon State University (B-P), 1977 (Reel 31, Frame 130)
    - Organization for Tropical Studies, Inc. (Santa Rosa), 1977 (Reel 31, Frame 136)
    - Op-Ox, 1977 (Reel 31, Frame 544)
    - Paine College, 1977 (Reel 31, Frame 658)
    - Patterson Foundation (Fellowship Awards), 1977 (Reel 31, Frame 681)
    - Pa, 1977 (Reel 31, Frame 806)
    - Pennsylvania State University (M-S), 1977 (Reel 31, Frame 915)
    - Pe, 1977 (Reel 31, Frame 963)
    - Phillips, Peter, 1977 (Reel 31, Frame 1018)
    - Planned Parenthood of New York City, Inc. (Sterilization Law Meeting), 1977 (Reel 32, Frame 1)
    - Ph-Pl, 1977 (Reel 32, Frame 191)
    - Population Council, Inc. (B-T), 1977 (Reel 32, Frame 270)
    - Princeton University (B-R), 1977 (Reel 32, Frame 399)
    - Po-Pr, 1977 (Reel 32, Frame 438)
    - Pu, 1977 (Reel 32, Frame 696)
    - Quinnipiac College (Health Symposia), 1977 (Reel 32, Frame 846)
    - Ra, 1977 (Reel 32, Frame 854)
    - Rea-Ren, 1977 (Reel 32, Frame 899)
    - Res-Rey, 1977 (Reel 32, Frame 1026)
    - Rh-Ri, 1977 (Reel 33, Frame 1)
    - Roberts Film Company (Ethnic Identity Series), 1977 (Reel 33, Frame 31)
    - Rockefeller, 1977 (Reel 33, Frame 54)
    - Rust College, 1977 (Reel 33, Frame 195)
    - Rutgers University (B-S), 1977 (Reel 33, Frame 209)
    - Ro-Ru, 1977 (Reel 33, Frame 230)
    - Saint (L-M), 1977 (Reel 33, Frame 501)
    - S-Sa, 1977 (Reel 33, Frame 536)
    - Sc, 1977 (Reel 33, Frame 788)
    - Se-Sh, 1977 (Reel 33, Frame 942)
    - Smithsonian Institution (B-U), 1977 (Reel 33, Frame 1080)
    - Si-Sn, 1977 (Reel 34, Frame 1)
    - Somers, Anne R., 1977 (Reel 34, Frame 150)
    - So-Sq, 1977 (Reel 34, Frame 362)
    - Stanford University (F-W), 1977 (Reel 34, Frame 701)
    - State University of New York at Albany (Humanities Conference), 1977 (Reel 34, Frame 795)
    - State University of New York at Stony Brook (Marine Environment), 1977 (Reel 34, Frame 801)
    - St-Sw, 1977 (Reel 34, Frame 842)
    - Texas Agricultural and Mechanical University (M-N), 1977 (Reel 35, Frame 1)
    - Texas Southern University (Sawyer, Granville M.), 1977 (Reel 35, Frame 60)
    - T-Te, 1977 (Reel 35, Frame 112)
    - Th, 1977 (Reel 35, Frame 382)
    - Ti-To, 1977 (Reel 35, Frame 650)
    - Tulane University (B-L), 1977 (Reel 35, Frame 811)
    - Tr-Tu, 1977 (Reel 35, Frame 857)
    - Union College, Kentucky, 1977 (Reel 36, Frame 1)
    - Union University, Tennessee, 1977 (Reel 36, Frame 24)
    - United Nations Association of Greater Boston and Massachusetts (Woetzel, Robert K.), 1977 (Reel 36, Frame 28)
    - United States, Agency for International Development (F-W), 1977 (Reel 36, Frame 105)
    - United States, Agriculture (A-W), 1977 (Reel 36, Frame 238)
    - United States, Environmental Protection Agency (Train, Russell E.), 1977 (Reel 36, Frame 662)
    - United States, General Accounting Office (International Exchange Programs Survey), 1977 (Reel 36, Frame 775)
    - United States (C-S), 1977 (Reel 36, Frame 803)
    - United States Commission on Civil Rights, 1977 (Reel 36, Frame 906)
    - United States Foundation for International Scouting, 1977 (Reel 36, Frame 911)
    - United States Gymnastics Federation, 1977 (Reel 36, Frame 917)
    - United States National Arboretum, 1977 (Reel 36, Frame 919)
    - United States Newspaper Project, 1977 (Reel 36, Frame 936)
    - United States Pharmacopeial Convention, 1977 (Reel 36, Frame 1090)
    - Universit Internacional, 1977 (Reel 36, Frame 1109)
    - University of Alaska (H-M), 1977 (Reel 36, Frame 1135)
    - University of Arizona (Chicana Oral History), 1977 (Reel 36, Frame 1196)
    - University of Arizona (A-H), 1977 (Reel 36, Frame 1203)
    - University of Arkansas (Parker, S. J.), 1977 (Reel 36, Frame 1217)
    - University of California (A-W), 1977 (Reel 37, Frame 1)
    - University of Chicago (B-L), 1977 (Reel 37, Frame 282)
    - University of Cincinnati (Bennis, Warren), 1977 (Reel 37, Frame 437)
    - University City Science Center, 1977 (Reel 37, Frame 444)
    - University of Colorado (B-W), 1977 (Reel 37, Frame 446)
    - University of Connecticut, 1977 (Reel 37, Frame 600)
    - University of Dallas (Center for Civic Leadership), 1977 (Reel 37, Frame 604)
    - University of Denver (M-R), 1977 (Reel 37, Frame 610)
    - University of Florida (I-V), 1977 (Reel 37, Frame 619)
    - University of Georgia (A-F), 1977 (Reel 37, Frame 685)
    - University of Hawaii (H-T), 1977 (Reel 37, Frame 707)
    - University Hospitals of Cleveland, 1977 (Reel 37, Frame 761)
    - University of Idaho (Laurence, Kenneth A.), 1977 (Reel 37, Frame 765)
    - University of Illinois (H-P), 1977 (Reel 37, Frame 770)
    - University of Iowa (I-J), 1977 (Reel 37, Frame 816)
    - University of Kentucky (Singletary, Otis), 1977 (Reel 37, Frame 903)
    - University of Maine (Canadian-American Studies Center), 1977 (Reel 37, Frame 906)
    - University of Maine (Franco-American Center), 1977 (Reel 37, Frame 908)
    - University of Maryland (Kuss, Fred R.), 1977 (Reel 37, Frame 974)
    - University of Massachusetts (A-I), 1977 (Reel 37, Frame 983)
    - University of Miami (H-P), 1977 (Reel 37, Frame 1019)
    - University of Michigan (A-S), 1977 (Reel 37, Frame 1024)
    - University of Minnesota (C-S), 1977 (Reel 38, Frame 1)
    - University of Missouri (E-M), 1977 (Reel 38, Frame 23)
    - University of New Hampshire (Dunn, G. M.), 1977 (Reel 38, Frame 52)
    - University of New Mexico (Women's Studies Program), 1977 (Reel 38, Frame 57)
    - University of North Carolina (I-P), 1977 (Reel 38, Frame 65)
    - University of Notre Dame, 1977 (Reel 38, Frame 76)
    - University of Oregon (Health Sciences Center), 1977 (Reel 38, Frame 105)
    - University of Pennsylvania (A-S), 1977 (Reel 38, Frame 115)
    - University Presses, 1977 (Reel 38, Frame 177)
    - University of Rochester (C-D), 1977 (Reel 38, Frame 189)
    - University of Southern California (A-C), 1977 (Reel 38, Frame 195)
    - University of Southwestern Louisiana (Women in Louisiana), 1977 (Reel 38, Frame 394)
    - University of Tennessee (Health Education), 1977 (Reel 38, Frame 399)
    - University of Texas (B-F), 1977 (Reel 38, Frame 410)
    - University of Utah (Native American Studies), 1977 (Reel 38, Frame 415)
    - University of Virginia (E-S), 1977 (Reel 38, Frame 417)
    - University of Washington, 1977 (Reel 38, Frame 533)
    - University of Wisconsin (B-Y), 1977 (Reel 38, Frame 535)
    - University of Wyoming (Policy Research Institute), 1977 (Reel 38, Frame 629)
    - Urbana College (Stickley, Thomas), 1977 (Reel 38, Frame 632)
    - Utah State University (B-T), 1977 (Reel 38, Frame 642)
    - U, 1977 (Reel 38, Frame 843)
    - Vanderbilt University (C-P), 1977 (Reel 38, Frame 870)
    - V, 1977 (Reel 38, Frame 910)
    - Wagner College (Cornell, C. David), 1977 (Reel 38, Frame 1071)
    - Wake Forest University (Language Center), 1977 (Reel 38, Frame 1075)
    - Washington University (B-P), 1977 (Reel 38, Frame 1081)
    - Wayne State University (Dorsey, John M.), 1977 (Reel 39, Frame 1)
    - W-Wa, 1977 (Reel 39, Frame 7)
    - We, 1977 (Reel 39, Frame 225)
    - Wh, 1977 (Reel 39, Frame 416)
    - Wiley and Sons, Inc., 1977 (Reel 39, Frame 584)
    - Winston-Salem State University, 1977 (Reel 39, Frame 675)
    - Wittenberg University (C-K), 1977 (Reel 39, Frame 680)
    - Wi, 1977 (Reel 39, Frame 688)
    - Wolf, Mary R., 1977 (Reel 39, Frame 966)
    - Women's Action Alliance, Inc., 1977 (Reel 40, Frame 1)
    - Work in America Institute (Rosow, Jerome M.), 1977 (Reel 40, Frame 226)
    - Worldwatch Institute (Brown, Lester R.), 1977 (Reel 40, Frame 261)
    - Wo, 1977 (Reel 40, Frame 533)
    - Wr-Wy, 1977 (Reel 40, Frame 825)
    - Yale University (F-K), 1977 (Reel 40, Frame 925)
    - X-Z, 1977 (Reel 41, Frame 1)
    - United States - Medical Sciences, 1977; 1977/200.A
      - Brown University, 1977 (Reel 41, Frame 133)
      - Georgetown University, 1977 (Reel 41, Frame 135)
      - Harvard University (C-P), 1977 (Reel 41, Frame 137)
      - Harvard University (Robert H. Ebert Fund), 1977 (Reel 41, Frame 188)
      - Indiana University, 1977 (Reel 41, Frame 297)
      - University of Buffalo, 1977 (Reel 41, Frame 299)
      - University of Chicago, 1977 (Reel 41, Frame 302)
      - University of Connecticut (Medical School), 1977 (Reel 41, Frame 308)
      - University of North Carolina, 1977 (Reel 41, Frame 321)
      - University of North Dakota (Native American Physicians), 1977 (Reel 41, Frame 323)
      - University of Pittsburgh, 1977 (Reel 41, Frame 325)
      - University of Rochester (Medical School), 1977 (Reel 41, Frame 327)
      - Wright State University, 1977 (Reel 41, Frame 356)
      - C-W, 1977 (Reel 41, Frame 358)
      - Yale University, 1977 (Reel 41, Frame 382)
      - Yeshiva University (Kuperman, Albert S.), 1977 (Reel 41, Frame 384)
    - United States - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1977; 1977/200.D
      - Cornell University (Agriculture), 1977 (Reel 41, Frame 386)
    - United States - Humanities and Arts, 1977; 1977/200.R
      - Artists and Performing Space (Conference), 1977 (Reel 41, Frame 415)
    - United States - Schistosomiasis, 1977; 1977/200.W
      - Clark Foundation (Biochemistry and Drug Development Meeting), 1977 (Reel 41, Frame 707)
  - Guam, 1977; 1977/213
    - University of Guam, 1977 (Reel 41, Frame 761)
  - Philippines, 1977; 1977/242
    - A-U, 1977 (Reel 41, Frame 773)
  - Puerto Rico, 1977; 1977/243
    - M-U, 1977 (Reel 41, Frame 868)
  - Internship Program - Minority School Superintendents, 1977; 1977/260
    - B-H, 1977 (Reel 41, Frame 964)
    - M-T, 1977 (Reel 41, Frame 979)
  - Fellowships in Higher Educational Administration (Minority), 1977; 1977/268
    - D-G, 1977 (Reel 41, Frame 1005)
  - Playwrights in Residence, 1977; 1977/272
    - A-K, 1977 (Reel 42, Frame 1)
    - L-Z, 1977 (Reel 42, Frame 279)
  - South America, 1977; 1977/300
    - F-N, 1977 (Reel 42, Frame 599)
    - South America - Medical Sciences, 1977; 1977/300.A
      - Pan American Federation of Medical Schools, 1977 (Reel 42, Frame 860)
    - South America - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1977; 1977/300.D
      - Agriculture, 1977 (Reel 42, Frame 929)
  - Argentina, 1977; 1977/301
    - Association for the Promotion of Family Schools of Agriculture, 1977 (Reel 42, Frame 1101)
  - Brazil, 1977; 1977/305
    - A-W, 1977 (Reel 43, Frame 1)
    - Brazil - Fellowships, 1977; 1977/305.E
      - Spinola, Ademario, 1977 (Reel 43, Frame 156)
  - Chile, 1977; 1977/309
    - Salmon Project, 1977 (Reel 43, Frame 163)
    - B-U, 1977 (Reel 43, Frame 325)
    - Chile - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1977; 1977/309.D
      - A-U, 1977 (Reel 43, Frame 343)
  - Colombia, 1977; 1977/311
    - Corporacion Centro Regional de Poblacion (Reproductive Biology), 1977 (Reel 43, Frame 366)
    - University of the Andes (Economic Research), 1977 (Reel 43, Frame 405)
    - University of the Andes, Economic Research (Supplementary Material), 1977 (Reel 43, Frame 431)
    - A-W, 1977 (Reel 43, Frame 865)
    - Colombia - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1977; 1977/311.D
      - Colombian Agricultural Institute, 1977 (Reel 43, Frame 1062)
  - Costa Rica, 1977; 1977/313
    - Carballo Quiros, Alfredo, 1977 (Reel 43, Frame 1066)
    - Costa Rica - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1977; 1977/313.D
      - Agriculture, 1977 (Reel 43, Frame 1069)
  - Ecuador, 1977; 1977/317
    - H-M, 1977 (Reel 43, Frame 1072)
    - Ecuador - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1977; 1977/317.D
      - Agriculture, 1977 (Reel 43, Frame 1086)
    - Ecuador - Fellowships, 1977; 1977/317.E
      - Diaz C., Gorky, 1977 (Reel 43, Frame 1089)
  - Guatemala, 1977; 1977/319
    - A-U, 1977 (Reel 43, Frame 1092)
  - Haiti, 1977; 1977/320
    - Centre de Recherches en Sciences Humaines et Sociales, 1977 (Reel 43, Frame 1112)
  - Mexico, 1977; 1977/323
    - A-V, 1977 (Reel 44, Frame 1)
    - Mexico - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1977; 1977/323.D
      - Agricultural Education (Monterrey), 1977 (Reel 44, Frame 148)
  - Nicaragua, 1977; 1977/325
    - C-N, 1977 (Reel 44, Frame 151)
  - Peru, 1977; 1977/331
    - D-V, 1977 (Reel 44, Frame 205)
  - El Salvador, 1977; 1977/333
    - D-M, 1977 (Reel 44, Frame 244)
  - Venezuela, 1977; 1977/339
    - I-M, 1977 (Reel 44, Frame 256)
    - Venezuela - Medical Sciences, 1977; 1977/339.A
      - Panamerican Federation of Medical Schools, 1977 (Reel 44, Frame 305)
    - Venezuela - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1977; 1977/339.D
      - 339D, 1977 (Reel 44, Frame 414)
      - Agriculture, 1977 (Reel 44, Frame 422)
  - Great Britain, 1977; 1977/400
    - Overseas Development (Dodd, W. A.), 1977 (Reel 44, Frame 425)
  - England, 1977; 1977/401
    - Institute of Development Studies (Lipton, Michael), 1977 (Reel 44, Frame 428)
    - A-K, 1977 (Reel 44, Frame 654)
    - University of Cambridge (B-E), 1977 (Reel 44, Frame 846)
    - University of Reading (Ellis, Peter R.), 1977 (Reel 44, Frame 868)
    - L-W, 1977 (Reel 44, Frame 893)
  - Ireland, 1977; 1977/403
    - B-T, 1977 (Reel 44, Frame 1063)
  - Scotland, 1977; 1977/405
    - P-U, 1977 (Reel 44, Frame 1098)
  - Malta, 1977; 1977/409
    - Peace Laboratory, Malta, 1977 (Reel 44, Frame 1131)
  - Australia, 1977; 1977/410
    - G-U, 1977 (Reel 45, Frame 1)
  - Fiji, 1977; 1977/419
    Includes Gilbert and Ellice Islands and Pitcairn Islands.
    - L-U, 1977 (Reel 45, Frame 37)
  - Caribbean Region and Central America, 1977; 1977/420
    - C-F, 1977 (Reel 45, Frame 122)
  - Canada, 1977; 1977/427
    - B-K, 1977 (Reel 45, Frame 155)
    - Penfield, Wilder G., 1977 (Reel 45, Frame 397)
    - University of British Columbia (A-E), 1977 (Reel 45, Frame 416)
    - University of Toronto (Burton, Ian), 1977 (Reel 45, Frame 474)
    - L-V, 1977 (Reel 45, Frame 580)
  - Bermuda, 1977; 1977/430
    - Bermuda Biological Station for Research (Wright, W. Redwood), 1977 (Reel 45, Frame 789)
  - Barbados, 1977; 1977/435
    - Bolden, Lindsey, 1977 (Reel 45, Frame 803)
  - Jamaica, 1977; 1977/437
    Including Caicos, Turks, and Caymen Islands.
    - C-G, 1977 (Reel 45, Frame 805)
  - Windward Islands, 1977/455
    - Windward Islands - Medical Sciences, 1977; 1977/455.A
      Windward Islands includes Dominica, Grenada, St. Lucia, and St. Vincent.
      - St. Lucia Planned Parenthood Association, 1977 (Reel 45, Frame 829)
  - Hong Kong, 1977; 1977/463
    - D, 1977 (Reel 45, Frame 834)
  - India, 1977; 1977/464
    - A-V, 1977 (Reel 45, Frame 841)
    - India - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1977; 1977/464.D
      - Agriculture, 1977 (Reel 45, Frame 996)
    - India - Fellowships, 1977; 1977/464.E
      - Aiyer, Mukundan S., 1977 (Reel 45, Frame 998)
  - Bengal/Bangladesh, 1977; 1977/466
    - Cholera Research Laboratory, 1977 (Reel 46, Frame 1)
  - New Guinea and Papua, 1977; 1977/472
    Including Solomon Islands.
    - Papua-New Guinea Institute of Applied Social and Economic Research (Conroy, J. D.), 1977 (Reel 46, Frame 175)
  - Malaysia, 1977; 1977/473
    - K-S, 1977 (Reel 46, Frame 196)
  - Africa, 1977; 1977/475
    - Association of Faculties of Science of African Universities, 1977 (Reel 46, Frame 210)
  - Kenya, 1977; 1977/476
    - C-S, 1977 (Reel 46, Frame 227)
    - University of Nairobi (E-P), 1977 (Reel 46, Frame 325)
    - Kenya - Fellowships, 1977; 1977/476.E
      - Kimuyu, Peter K., 1977 (Reel 46, Frame 381)
  - East Africa Region, 1977; 1977/477
    - E-R, 1977 (Reel 46, Frame 383)
  - Rhodesia, 1977; 1977/483
    - Whitson Foundation, 1977 (Reel 46, Frame 391)
  - South Africa Region, 1977; 1977/487
    - L-N, 1977 (Reel 46, Frame 398)
    - South Africa Region - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1977; 1977/487.D
      - Agriculture, 1977 (Reel 46, Frame 402)
  - Cape of Good Hope, 1977; 1977/489
    - G-M, 1977 (Reel 46, Frame 479)
    - Cape of Good Hope - Medical Sciences, 1977; 1977/489.A
      - University of Witwatersrand (Medical School), 1977 (Reel 46, Frame 487)
  - Uganda, 1977; 1977/492
    - A-M, 1977 (Reel 46, Frame 494)
  - Sudan, 1977; 1977/494
    - E-H, 1977 (Reel 46, Frame 532)
    - University of Khartoum (Rasheed, Sadig), 1977 (Reel 46, Frame 548)
    - Sudan - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1977; 1977/494.D
      - Agriculture, 1977 (Reel 46, Frame 615)
    - Sudan - Fellowships, 1977; 1977/494.E
      - 494E, 1977 (Reel 46, Frame 627)
  - West Africa, 1977; 1977/495
    - R-W, 1977 (Reel 46, Frame 693)
    - West Africa - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1977; 1977/495.D
      - Agriculture, 1977 (Reel 46, Frame 703)
  - Ghana, 1977; 1977/496
    - A-C, 1977 (Reel 46, Frame 710)
    - University of Ghana (P-T), 1977 (Reel 46, Frame 729)
    - Ghana - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1977; 1977/496.D
      - Agriculture, 1977 (Reel 46, Frame 867)
  - Nigeria, 1977; 1977/497
    - University of Ibadan (A-T), 1977 (Reel 46, Frame 871)
    - A-U, 1977 (Reel 47, Frame 1)
    - Nigeria - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1977; 1977/497.D
      - Agriculture, 1977 (Reel 47, Frame 112)
  - France, 1977; 1977/500
    - A-R, 1977 (Reel 47, Frame 114)
  - Asia, 1977; 1977/600
    - Asia/Pacific Food Production Conference, 1977 (Reel 47, Frame 352)
    - Asia - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1977; 1977/600.D
      - Corn, 1977 (Reel 47, Frame 363)
  - Taiwan, 1977; 1977/605
    - A-N, 1977 (Reel 47, Frame 368)
  - Japan, 1977; 1977/609
    - H-T, 1977 (Reel 47, Frame 381)
  - Korea, 1977; 1977/613
    - M-Y, 1977 (Reel 47, Frame 413)
    - Korea - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1977; 1977/613.D
      - Agriculture, 1977 (Reel 47, Frame 455)
  - Thailand, 1977; 1977/617
    - A-B, 1977 (Reel 47, Frame 457)
    - C, 1977 (Reel 47, Frame 680)
    - K-W, 1977 (Reel 47, Frame 962)
    - Thailand - Fellowships, 1977; 1977/617.E
      - C-V, 1977 (Reel 48, Frame 1)
    - Thailand - Social Sciences, 1977; 1977/617.S
      - University of Thammasat (Economics), 1977 (Reel 48, Frame 82)
  - Holland, 1977; 1977/650
    - D-P, 1977 (Reel 48, Frame 89)
  - Indonesia, 1977; 1977/652
    - A-S, 1977 (Reel 48, Frame 159)
    - Indonesia - Fellowships, 1977; 1977/652.E
      - M-P, 1977 (Reel 48, Frame 220)
  - Surinam, 1977; 1977/659.A
    Formerly Dutch Guiana
    - University of Surinam, 1977 (Reel 48, Frame 226)
  - Ethiopia, 1977; 1977/701
    - Deguefu, Dawit, 1977 (Reel 48, Frame 231)
  - Belgium, 1977; 1977/707
    - C-U, 1977 (Reel 48, Frame 236)
  - Belgian Congo, 1977; 1977/709
    - Mudimbe, Vumbi Yoka, 1977 (Reel 48, Frame 250)
    - A-W, 1977 (Reel 48, Frame 313)
    - Belgian Congo - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1977; 1977/709.D
      - Maize Improvement, 1977 (Reel 48, Frame 372)
    - Belgian Congo - Fellowships, 1977; 1977/709.E
      - Luvwezo, Mabikwa, 1977 (Reel 48, Frame 379)
      - C-T, 1977 (Reel 48, Frame 452)
  - Yugoslavia, 1977; 1977/710
    - Ban, Sinisa, 1977 (Reel 48, Frame 499)
  - Denmark, 1977; 1977/713
    - N-T, 1977 (Reel 48, Frame 505)
  - Germany, 1977; 1977/717
    - F-V, 1977 (Reel 48, Frame 513)
  - Tanganyika, 1977; 1977/723
    - B-U, 1977 (Reel 48, Frame 621)
  - Cameroon, 1977; 1977/735
    - D-U, 1977 (Reel 48, Frame 783)
  - Greece, 1977; 1977/749
    - A-T, 1977 (Reel 48, Frame 829)
  - Hungary, 1977; 1977/750
    - Institute for Water Resources Development (Vermes, L.), 1977 (Reel 48, Frame 949)
  - Italy, 1977; 1977/751
    - C-N, 1977 (Reel 48, Frame 951)
  - Tripoli, 1977; 1977/758
    - Zagalli, Farida, 1977 (Reel 49, Frame 1)
  - Liberia, 1977; 1977/759
    - F-L, 1977 (Reel 49, Frame 3)
  - Norway, 1977; 1977/767
    - Christian Michelsen Institute (Faaland, Just), 1977 (Reel 49, Frame 20)
  - Iran, 1977; 1977/771
    - Imperial Medical Center, 1977 (Reel 49, Frame 87)
  - Portugal, 1977; 1977/773
    - A-U, 1977 (Reel 49, Frame 115)
    - Portugal - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1977; 1977/773.D
      - Agriculture (January-February), 1977 (Reel 49, Frame 129)
      - Agriculture (March-December), 1977 (Reel 50, Frame 1)
  - Finland, 1977; 1977/787
    - League of Finnish American Societies, 1977 (Reel 50, Frame 239)
  - Poland, 1977; 1977/789
    - Rolicka, Mary, 1977 (Reel 50, Frame 245)
  - Spain, 1977; 1977/795
    - H-L, 1977 (Reel 50, Frame 247)
  - Sweden, 1977; 1977/800
    - B-U, 1977 (Reel 50, Frame 328)
  - Switzerland, 1977; 1977/803
    - S-U, 1977 (Reel 50, Frame 355)
  - Turkey, 1977; 1977/805
    - A-R, 1977 (Reel 50, Frame 479)
  - Egypt, 1977; 1977/812
    - M-S, 1977 (Reel 50, Frame 500)
  - Saudi Arabia and Oman, 1977; 1977/817
    - King Faisal Philanthropic Foundation, 1977 (Reel 50, Frame 528)
  - Kuwait, 1977; 1977/822
    - Sabah Charitable Foundation, 1977 (Reel 50, Frame 531)
  - Israel, 1977; 1977/825
    - I-W, 1977 (Reel 50, Frame 535)
    - Israel - Medical Sciences, 1977; 1977/825.A
      - Ben Gurion University, 1977 (Reel 50, Frame 668)
  - Lebanon, 1977; 1977/833
    - A, 1977 (Reel 50, Frame 695)
    - Lebanon - Medical Sciences, 1977; 1977/833.A
      - American University of Beirut (H-L), 1977 (Reel 50, Frame 708)
  - Members and Meetings, 1977; 1977/903
    - H-W, 1977 (Reel 50, Frame 746)
  - Humanities, 1977; 1977/911
    - B-M, 1977 (Reel 50, Frame 826)
    - N-W, 1977 (Reel 50, Frame 971)
    - Humanities - Fellowships, 1977; 1977/911.E
      - B-J, 1977 (Reel 50, Frame 1033)
      - K-Z, 1977 (Reel 50, Frame 1152)
  - Environmental Affairs, 1977/927
    - Environmental Affairs - Fellowships, 1977; 1977/927.E
      - L-W, 1977 (Reel 50, Frame 1323)
- General Correspondence, 1978
  - International, 1978; 1978/100
    - Allen, Jane, 1978 (Reel 1, Frame 1)
    - Almy, Susan W., 1978 (Reel 1, Frame 5)
    - Anderson, Bernard E., 1978 (Reel 1, Frame 18)
    - Arbab, Farzam, 1978 (Reel 1, Frame 38)
    - Barnish, Guy, 1978 (Reel 1, Frame 72)
    - Bartholomew, Richard K., 1978 (Reel 1, Frame 78)
    - Benson, Peter, 1978 (Reel 1, Frame 93)
    - Biggs, Tyler S., 1978 (Reel 1, Frame 100)
    - Black, Joseph E., 1978 (Reel 1, Frame 104)
    - Bookmyer, Joseph R., 1978 (Reel 1, Frame 108)
    - Borlaug, Norman E., 1978 (Reel 1, Frame 110)
    - Bronte, D. Lydia, 1978 (Reel 1, Frame 115)
    - Bruer, John, 1978 (Reel 1, Frame 121)
    - Buhr, Kenneth L., 1978 (Reel 1, Frame 124)
    - Celli, Roberto, 1978 (Reel 1, Frame 144)
    - Christie, John D., 1978 (Reel 1, Frame 148)
    - Coleman, James S., 1978 (Reel 1, Frame 162)
    - Colton, Joel, 1978 (Reel 1, Frame 170)
    - Connell, Elizabeth B., 1978 (Reel 1, Frame 252)
    - Court, David, 1978 (Reel 1, Frame 275)
    - Deagle, Edwin A., Jr., 1978 (Reel 1, Frame 278)
    - Dinning, James S., 1978 (Reel 1, Frame 293)
    - Douglas, Johnson E., 1978 (Reel 1, Frame 296)
    - Durana, Ines, 1978 (Reel 1, Frame 325)
    - Finfrock, Dwight C., 1978 (Reel 1, Frame 355)
    - Freeman, Wayne H., 1978 (Reel 1, Frame 372)
    - Garfield, Susan, 1978 (Reel 1, Frame 374)
    - Gasbarre, Louis C., 1978 (Reel 1, Frame 376)
    - Goffman, William, 1978 (Reel 1, Frame 456)
    - Goodgame, Richard W., 1978 (Reel 1, Frame 458)
    - Grant, Ulysses J., 1978 (Reel 1, Frame 467)
    - Greenfield, Beth, 1978 (Reel 1, Frame 475)
    - Harrar, J. George, 1978 (Reel 1, Frame 478)
    - Harwood, Roland E., 1978 (Reel 1, Frame 495)
    - Heaton, Herbert, 1978 (Reel 1, Frame 527)
    - Hildebrand, Peter E., 1978 (Reel 1, Frame 530)
    - House, Leland R., 1978 (Reel 1, Frame 534)
    - Jackson, Ben R., 1978 (Reel 1, Frame 551)
    - Jennings, Peter R., 1978 (Reel 1, Frame 593)
    - Johnson, Loyd, 1978 (Reel 1, Frame 614)
    - Johnston, James E., 1978 (Reel 1, Frame 630)